AMBER SWARTZ

Sedro-Woolley, WA 98284

Phone: 360-420-0434 | **Email**: <u>asriley144@gmail.com</u>

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/amber-swartz-081a691ab/ | GitHub: github.com/ASwartz14

Portfolio: aswartz14.github.io/BootstrapPortfolio/

SUMMARY

I am a Full Stack Web Developer with a keen interest in UI/UX. I have team management experience, customer service skills, meticulous attention to detail, and creative problem solving skills.. I am a driven, an ambitious forward thinker that learns and evolves quickly and will be an asset to your team. Now armed with skills in mobile first web development, I am ready to utilize all of my skills in an exciting new Web Development position.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Foundation, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, & Handelbars.js

PROJECTS

WHAT'S FOR DINNER

Deployed Link: https://cynthiwu.github.io/whats-for-dinner/

GitHub Repo: https://github.com/cynthiwu/whats-for-dinner

Description: Web based application that generates recipe ideas based on users input of

ingredients. Designed with mobile users in mind it also allows many options

for the user to tailor to their needs.

Responsibilities: I was responsible for doing frontend javascript for this project.

DAY PLANNER

Deployed Link: https://aswartz14.github.io/DayPlanner/

GitHub Repo: https://github.com/ASwartz14/DayPlanner

Description: Web based application designed mobile first that keeps track of your daily

tasks dynamically updated time block color to indicate past, present, or

future tasks.

Responsibilities: I did all aspects of this project

WORK EXPERIENCE

Owner/Manager

Ohana Gardens - Anacortes, WA January 2018 to September 2019

I bought a failing i502 recreational cannabis grow with only 36 plants with no customers and not paying bills, and turned it into 400 plants with customers, and paying bills. I did everything myself. Garden chores, cleaning, bookkeeping, data entry, sales, customer service, deliveries, purchasing, and packaging. I sold to Floyd's, PRC, and Cannazone. I was forced to shut it down after having a large sum of money stolen from me. I didn't seek other employment after as I found out I was pregnant and ended up on bed rest.

Owner/Operator

Uber Partner Drivers - Bellingham, WA May 2017 to April 2018

I operated my car for ride-share for Uber and lyft F/T until I was too busy with my other business.

Garden/Nursery Manager

Herbin Harvest - Arlington, WA August 2016 to May 2017

I managed the mother room, vegetation room, and clone room, for a large i502 cannabis grow. We got contamination from another grow, the owner switched to unclean methods, I quit and started driving Uber/lyft. Now the company no longer exists because of the unclean practices.

Operations Assistant

Treacy Levine Center - Lake McMurray, WA April 2015 to June 2016

I was responsible for the management and scheduling of daily maintenance tasks as well as long term maintenance and management for 200 acre camp, operations of excavator and backhoe, scheduling and data entry, customer and vendor relations, purchasing and ordering, gardening, animal care, general labor and maintenance, and management of maintenance crew when maintenance manager was gone. In May 2016 the camp announced that they would be selling in June and there would be no more employment.

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate: University of Washington, Seattle, WA

A 24-week program focused on gaining programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.